twcc.com 2018-08-23

# Charter Spectrum - Website Privacy Policy

* * *

This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for the website, any subdomains and its various related features (together referred to as the "site"). Charter Communications (referred to as "Charter," "us" or "we") is committed to protecting your privacy while on this site. Please read the information below to learn how we collect, use and disclose the information gathered by this site.

You acknowledge that by accessing or using our site, you agree to be bound by all of the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site.

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Such changes, modifications, additions, or deletions shall become effective immediately upon posting. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this site and this Privacy Policy periodically, and to be aware of any modifications. Your continued use of the site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by the Privacy Policy as modified.

## Are You a Charter Customer?

This Privacy Policy only applies to your use of this site. This Privacy Policy does not govern Charter's treatment of information it collects, uses or discloses other than through this site. If you are looking for Charter's residential subscriber service agreement, acceptable use policy or other Charter residential subscriber policies, please click here: [Charter Residential Subscriber Policies.](https://www.spectrum.com/policies/your-privacy-rights.html) If you are looking for Charter's commercial acceptable use policy or terms of service, please click here: [Charter Commercial Subscriber Policies](https://www.spectrum.com/policies/your-privacy-rights.html). If you are looking for Charter's residential cable television, high-speed Internet or telephone privacy policies, please click here: [Charter Residential Subscriber Privacy Policies](https://www.spectrum.com/policies/your-privacy-rights.html). If you are looking for Charter's commercial cable television, high-speed Internet or telephone privacy policies, please click here: [Charter Commercial Subscriber Privacy Policies](https://www.spectrum.com/policies/your-privacy-rights.html).

## Types of Information Collected

In order to provide this site and our numerous services, we collect two types of information on our site: Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information. Our primary goal in collecting information from you is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience while using our site.

Personally Identifiable Information: This refers to information that identifies you specifically. When you engage in certain activities on this site, such as registering for a membership, ordering a product or service, submitting content and/or posting content in discussion forums or other public areas, entering a contest or sweepstakes, filling out a survey, or sending us feedback, we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities; however, we may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, telephone and fax numbers, and other personally identifying information. When ordering products or services on the site, you may also be asked to provide payment information. Depending upon the activity, some of the information we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information: This refers to information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. This information is compiled and analyzed on both an individual and an aggregated basis. This information may include the Web site's Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") that you just came from, which URL you go to next, demographic information, what browser you are using, and/or your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. A URL is the global address of documents and other resources on the World Wide Web. An IP address is an identifier for a computer or device on a network, such as the World Wide Web. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web, allowing Web servers to locate and identify your computer. Computers require IP addresses in order for users to communicate on the Internet.

## Collection Methods and Use of Information

We do not collect any Personally Identifiable Information about you on this site unless you voluntarily provide it to us. You provide certain Personally Identifiable Information to us when you (a) register for our services and register your e-mail address with us; (b) enter sweepstakes or contests sponsored by us or one of our partners; (c) sign up for special offers from us or from selected third parties; (d) send e-mail messages, submit forms, post to forums, or transmit other information by telephone, e-mail or letter; or (e) submit your payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services on our site. We may also collect information from you at other points on our site that state that such information is being collected.

In addition, we, or our third-party ad server and/or content server may collect, certain Non-Personally Identifiable Information. We use your IP address to diagnose problems with our servers and/or software, to administer our site, and to gather demographic information. Our third-party ad servers may also provide us with summary, but not individual, reports that will tell us how many ads were presented and clicked upon at our site.

We will primarily use your Personally Identifiable Information to (a) to provide our services to you; (b) to allow us to properly maintain this site and our services and to make improvements or upgrades when necessary; (c) to provide you with technical support and for system maintenance; (d) to inform you of new products or services that may be of interest to you; (e) to respond to your inquiries or send administrative notices; (f) to prevent fraud, including the unauthorized use of this site or our services or violations of applicable policies and terms of service; or (g) to ensure our own compliance with the law. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, and enforce our agreements with you, including any website terms of use or this Privacy Policy.

## Release of Information

We do not sell, trade, or rent your Personally Identifiable Information to unaffiliated third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless you have affirmatively agreed to such disclosure. Charter may disclose your Personally Identifiable Information with some of our same-branded affiliates for those affiliates" direct marketing purposes. We do provide some of our services or provide parts of this site through contractual arrangements with affiliates, services providers, partners, and other third parties. We and our service partners may use your Personally Identifiable Information to deliver these services and to operate our site.

As part of our business activities, if we enter into a merger, acquisition or sale of all or a portion of our assets, we may transfer your Personally Identifiable Information associated with the transaction.

Occasionally, we may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide Personally Identifiable Information to the appropriate governmental authorities. We may disclose Personally Identifiable Information upon receipt of a court order or subpoena, to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation, or when otherwise permitted by applicable law. We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use this site for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful.

## User Choices on Collection and Use of Information

If you do not wish to provide Personally Identifiable Information on this site, then you should not provide it when requested or otherwise provide your information to this site. However, some parts of this site or our service may not function without the requested information. We may, from time to time, send you marketing messages (e.g., email, direct mail, telephone calls, etc.) regarding our products and services. If you do not want to receive these marketing messages from Charter, please follow the opt-out instructions in the message or designate your Charter opt-out request by visiting [Charter's Privacy Policy](https://www.spectrum.com/policies/your-privacy-rights.html). For more information about targeted marketing see below.

## Security of Information

Charter takes the security of your Personally Identifiable Information seriously. We take such actions as are reasonably necessary to prevent unauthorized access by entities other than Charter and its service providers to Personally Identifiable Information. Charter uses security and/or encryption technology to secure certain sensitive Personally Identifiable Information when it collects such information over this site. Charter restricts access to its customer database and secures the content by use of firewalls and other security methods. Charter limits access to databases containing Personally Identifiable Information to authorized employees and agents of Charter and other parties identified in the use and release sections above.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personally Identifiable Information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control; (b) the security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this site cannot be guaranteed; and (c) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with by a third party while in transit.

You need to help protect the privacy of your own information. You should not give Personally Identifiable Information to strangers or others whom you are not certain have a right or need to the information. You also must take precautions to protect the security of any Personally Identifiable Information that you may transmit by using encryption and other techniques to help prevent unauthorized parties from intercepting or receiving any of your Personally Identifiable Information. You are responsible for the security of your information when using unencrypted, open access or otherwise unsecured networks in your home or elsewhere. Charter will never ask you to provide account sign-in passwords, credit card numbers, or other sensitive information through unsolicited email messages. If we request such information from you, we will always direct you to Charter's website, call you directly or ask that you give us a call. You should, however, be aware of imposter websites pretending to be Charter's. If you have receive an email requesting that you sign in or provide information that you suspect was not sent by Charter, DO NOT CLICK ON THE LINK IN THE EMAIL but use your own browser to go to Charter's site. If you are directed to a website that you do not believe is Charter's, please forward the full email (with full Internet headers) to [phishing@spectrum.net](mailto:phishing@spectrum.net). Charter will also not ask for your Internet account password over the telephone.

## Cookies and Targeted Marketing

When you use our site we may store cookies on your computer in order to facilitate and customize your use of our site. A cookie is a small data text file, which a website stores on your computer's hard drive (if your Web browser permits) that can later be retrieved to identify you to us. Our cookies may store Personally Identifiable Information and/or Non-Personally Identifiable Information about you, your computer, or your preferences so that you may more easily use our site. The cookies make the site run more smoothly and help us to maintain a more secure site. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but some parts of our site may not work properly in that case.

Charter wants to make its website and its advertisements for its goods and services more relevant to You. Charter collects and uses non-personal information, such as information about your visits to our websites and IP address, and personally identifiable information, such as information You provide Charter and from Your Charter account (see "Types of Information Collected"), to identify and present such tailored advertisements for Charter's goods and services. In addition, Charter partners with one or more third-party advertising companies who may utilize cookies, web beacons, or other technology to deliver or facilitate the delivery of targeted advertisements about Charter's goods and services on third-party websites. Charter will not provide this partner with access to Your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number or other personally identifiable information. When these targeted online advertisements are based on Your personally identifiable information and displayed on third-party websites, You may opt-out by going to [Charter's Privacy Policy](https://pc2.mypreferences.com/Charter/Privacy) and requesting to have your privacy preferences updated. After doing so, we recommend that You also remove any unwanted cookies from Your browser. For more information on how to adjust these settings go to Charter.com > Support > Internet Help. Because a "Do Not Track" protocol has not yet been finalized, this site"s information collection and disclosure practices, and the choices that it provides to consumers, will continue to operate as described in this Privacy Policy, whether or not a Do Not Track signal is received.

Third-party ad serving companies and other unaffiliated advertisers also display advertisements on our site. As part of their service, they may place a separate cookie on your computer or utilize other means, such as, web beacons, clear GIFs, pixel tags or other similar technologies, to collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information, such as your IP address, browser type, the server your computer is logged onto, the area code and zip code associated with your server, and whether you responded to a particular advertisement.

## Links to Third-Party Sites

Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we directly collect from you. Other sites accessible through our site have their own privacy policies and data collection, use, and disclosure practices. Please consult each site's privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties. Additionally, other companies which place advertising on our site may collect information about you when you view or click on their advertising through the use of cookies. We cannot control this collection of information. You should contact these advertisers or sites directly if you have any questions about their use of the information that they collect.

## Note to California Customers Regarding Your Privacy Rights

California law requires Charter provide to you, upon request, certain information regarding the sharing of Personally Identifiable Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. As mentioned above, Charter does not share Personally Identifiable Information with unaffiliated third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. However, Charter may share Personally Identifiable Information with some same-branded affiliates for those affiliates" direct marketing purposes. If you make a request by using the below Website Privacy methods of contact, Charter will provide you with the number of its same-branded affiliates in California and a list of Personally Identifiable Information that it may have shared with some or all such same-branded affiliates.

## Miscellaneous Privacy Issues

Except where expressly indicated, this site is directed towards adults and you must be at least 18 years old to submit any Personally Identifiable Information to this site. We do not knowingly collect, use, or disclose Personally Identifiable Information about visitors that are under 18 years of age unless expressly specified on the applicable pages of the site. Some third-party features provided on or linked to on our site may collect some Personally Identifiable Information on individuals younger than 18 years old. Such collection and information is subject to the terms and conditions and privacy policy of those parties" sites or services and, as required by applicable law, may require consent from a parent or guardian. Children should always get permission from a parent or guardian before sending any information about themselves over the Internet to Charter or anyone else.

You should also be aware that when Personally Identifiable Information is voluntarily disclosed (i.e. your name, e-mail address, etc.) in any discussion forums or other public areas on this site, that information, along with any information disclosed in your communication, can be collected and used by third parties and may result in unsolicited messages from third parties. Such activities are beyond our control and this Privacy Policy does not apply to such information. Any submissions to public areas on this site are accepted with the understanding that they are accessible to all third parties. If you do not want your comments to be viewed by third parties, you are advised not to make any submissions. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your password and/or account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online.

We use a third party provider to place our internet ads. The provider may collect anonymous information about your visits to our site and your interaction with our products and services. The provider may also use information about your visits to this and other sites to target advertisements for merchandise and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag which is industry standard technology used by most major websites. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process. The provider does not know your name, address, phone number, email address or any of your other personally identifiable information. If you would like more information about this practice and your option to not have this anonymous information used by our third party provider, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/#completed). To opt-out of these ads click on [this link](http://media.charter.com/optout.html).

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the privacy practices of this site, please contact us by sending a letter or email to:

Charter Communications  
Attn: Legal Department, Website Privacy  
12405 Powerscourt Drive  
Saint Louis, Missouri 63131  
privacy@charter.com

If you have any questions about our services, your dealings with this site or to contact someone about the services offered by Charter, please contact us by calling (833) 267-6097.

Effective: December 16, 2013
